abcdistributing.com 2005-12-30

# Welcome to Online Shopping with abc!

In the event that abcdistributing.com amends its Privacy Policy in the future, these changes will be clearly posted on our web site so you can be kept informed of how, where, when and why we collect information and how we use it. Once posted, the new policy will go into effect immediately, replacing any previously stated policy.

Return to top

If you request a catalog, we will need your name, the name of the company you work for and a company address where we should send the catalog. We will also ask for a phone number we can use to contact you if any of the information provided is incorrect (for example, if there is a typographical error.) If you wish to set up an account and purchase merchandise from us, we may ask for additional information. 

When you visit our Web site we may collect more information such as your Internet service provider's address, the name of the Website directing you, or your viewing activity on our site. This data helps us understand how to make our site more useful and user friendly to you, our customer. 

We use a third party service provider to help us gather and analyze information about our customers. The role of this third party is to help conduct our business and deliver the most relevant products and services. If you would like to deactivate our ability to analyze your anonymous browsing and purchase behavior through the use of this service or find out more about our service provider, including its privacy policy and how to opt out, go to: <http://www.coremetrics.com/info_eluminate2.html>. 

Return to top

"Cookies" are small pieces of data that are stored in the memory of your browser, and on the hard drive of your computer. A cookie is used to identify you when you return to our site. This makes your visit more personalized and convenient. When you are ready to place an order, we use cookies to pre-fill out certain parts of the order form, such as your name, address and account number, making it easier for you. They also allow you to place items in your shopping cart, leave the website, and then return to check out at a later time. In addition, once you log in to our Online Service Center, we use a cookie to check your identification each time you ask for a transaction, to ensure that we do not release information on your account to unauthorized individuals. If you do not have cookies enabled on your machine, you will not be able to use the Online Service Center.

Return to top

abc distributing, LLC collects your e-mail address as part of your registration with us. We use this address to communicate with you about your account, and, if you wish, to send you notices that might be of interest to you. We do not sell or otherwise give out your e-mail address to others. None of your information is merged with outside data for marketing purposes. 

If at any time you wish to be removed from our e-mail mailing list, please call our Customer Service Department at (305) 944-6971, or follow the link provided in the disclaimer of our promotional emails. But before you do, think about all the great values and special offers you�ll be missing.

Return to top

Yes. The security of your personal information is very important to us. In our efforts to protect your online transactions, we use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If your browser is capable of SSL (and most are), your personal information will be automatically encrypted, or encoded, before it is sent over the Internet. Also, we store your information behind a firewall and it is not available to unauthorized computers.

Return to top

Once you make a purchase from our online store, your name becomes a part of our customer file. As a valued abc distributing, LLC customer, you will receive catalog mailings from us in the future.

Return to top

abc distributing, LLC is committed to the security of information collected on our site. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Private account information is located behind a firewall; it is not directly connected to the Internet. Information behind the firewall on the customer server is not available to unauthorized computers. The firewall is a recognized industry standard and exceeds the standards set by the International Computer Security Association, an industry authority on Internet security.

Return to top

abc distributing, LLC does not sell products for purchase by children. Children are not allowed to open accounts with us. If you are a child who may have accessed this website, please make sure that a parent knows that you are visiting us and ask for their help. Please have your parent read this information with you.

If parents have any inquiries about the abc distributing, LLC Children's Privacy Policy, please contact our legal department [via e-mail](mailto:custservice@abcdistributing.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy) or at the following address: 

abc distributing, LLC  
Legal Department  
6301 East 10th Avenue  
Hialeah, FL 33012

**Parents:** abc distributing, LLC encourages you to ensure that your child's use of an access to [www.abcdistributing.com](http://www.abcdistributing.com/) is under your supervision and within the guidelines that only you have established for them. 

Return to top
